[{"answer": "I didn't volunteer", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " No trouble", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What kind of information", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Change what", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I see.  You don't remember assaulting a police officer...several officers", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You don't have a driver's license, my friend?  Or a Social Security card", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hiding", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What's wonderful about the air, my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "This is April, right", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " July?", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " July?", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What year is it", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Do you know what year it is", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What year do you think it is", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You think it's July of 1995?  That's the future, my friend.  Do you think you're living in the future", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "1995 is the future, my friend.  This is 1989", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Lemme see your head, my friend, see if you got any creepy crawlies", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Gotta work that out with a doctor, my friend. Can't make no calls 'til the doctor says", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Does this bother you, Mr. my friend", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Who would you call, Mr. my friend, who would straighten everything out", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Now", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " YES", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I didn't think I was being defensive. I was just..", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Okay, it was bad judgment.  But I have the strangest feeling about him", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You were in my dream just now.  Your hair was different, but I'm sure it was you", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "About an airport...before everything happened.  It's the same dream I always have", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "About an airport...before everything happened.  It's the same dream I always have", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You were very upset.  You're always very upset in the dream, but I never knew it was you before", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Hey, I know what you're thinking.  You're thinking I don't exist except in your head.  I can see that point of view.  But you could still talk to me, couldn't you? Carry on a decent conversation", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Why would I pull out my teeth, my friend? They don't like that.  That's a n", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yelling won't get you what you want.  You have to be smart to get what you want", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You don't know what you want?  Sure you do, my friend.  You know what you want", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Okay...you were standing there looking at the moon...you were eating grass... then what", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Just like that?  You were in prison", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I thought I was in...prison again", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No, not really.  It's...it's in my mind.  Like you said", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You disappeared!  One minute you were there, the next minute you were gone. Did you run through the woods", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "The boy in the well.  How did you know that was just a hoax", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "It was?  I didn't...know", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "my friend, you said he was hiding in the barn..", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "IT WASN'T A TV SHOW!  IT WAS REAL", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Nine thirt", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " Tight?  My watch says ", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "How did you find me", "docId": "12-Monkeys.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "The call I just made?  Five minutes ago", "qsentId": 46}]